<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yixin Liu</title>
    <link>http://yixin-liu.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yixin Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yixin-liu.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All hands on deck: The role of collaborative platforms and lead organizations in achieving environmental goals</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/ccc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/ccc/</guid>
      <description>This paper combines the difference-in-differences (DiD) methods and content analysis to examine the effectiveness of collaborative platforms in supporting local collaborations for natural resource management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust and Two-way Coproduction: Paired Experiments on Citizens and Policymakers</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/tw_coproduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/tw_coproduction/</guid>
      <description>This paper conducts a paired of experiments on citizens and municipal policymakers to examine the impacts of trust in government on coproductioin in disaster resilience planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The “Watershed” of Collaboration: The Impact of Legislation and Collaborative Actions on Environmental Outcomes</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/orwater/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/orwater/</guid>
      <description>This paper combines the regression discontinuity in time (RDiT) design and longitudinal analysis to examine the impacts of state legislation and the subsequent collaborative projects on water quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How and when democratic values matter: Challenging the effectiveness-centric framework in program evaluation</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/value/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/value/</guid>
      <description>Using a conjoint experiment, this research compare the effects of effectiveness and democratic values in predicting public program evaluation, conditioned on citizens’ trust in government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partisan Collaboration in Policy Adoption: A Preliminary Experimental Study with Local Government Officials</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/localexp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/localexp/</guid>
      <description>This paper uses a conjoint experiment involving U.S. municipal officials to test the co-partisanship effect on policy collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public trust and collaborative governance: An instrumental variable approach</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/trust/</guid>
      <description>This research utilizes public integrity information, randomly assigned as the instrumental variable, to explore the impact of trust in government on citizens&amp;rsquo; perceptions of collaborative governance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effectiveness of network administrative organizations in governing inter-jurisdictional natural resources</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/rcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/rcs/</guid>
      <description>This paper uses the synthetic control method, incorporating monthly water quality data from 14 river monitoring sites in two neighboring cities, to examine the effectiveness of the Network Administrative Organization (NAO) model in reducing water pollution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De-stereotyping public performance evaluation</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/je/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/je/</guid>
      <description>This paper employs a series of experiments to examine the relationship between performance information and the evaluation mode, suggesting that presenting information jointly (joint evaluation), rather than separately (separate evaluation), may assist people in avoiding stereotyping and focusing on actual performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Administration in American Society</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/c1/</guid>
      <description>This course, taught at Florida State University from Fall 2021 to Spring 2022, introduced students to the fundamental theories and practices of public administration. Topics covered included social equity, public ethics, organizational theory, politics and management, public finance, performance management, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does mislabeling COVID-19 elicit the perception of threat and reduce blame?</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/covid/</guid>
      <description>This paper employs a list experiment to examine whether mislabeling COVID-19 as the &amp;lsquo;Chinese Virus&amp;rsquo; has incited opposition towards Chinese immigrants and reduced public blame attributed to the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Lectures</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/c2/</guid>
      <description>This page gathers information about the guest lectures I have provided for both master and doctoral level graduate students.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
