<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on Yixin Liu</title>
    <link>http://yixin-liu.com/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on Yixin Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yixin-liu.com/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Environmental Policy</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/envpolicy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/envpolicy/</guid>
      <description>This course explores environmental politics and policy, with a focus on the United States. It covers environmental, energy, and natural resource issues, public opinion, and the forces shaping policymaking and implementation. Key topics include policy analysis, the role of the environmental community, and selected U.S. and global environmental policy issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Budgeting</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/budget/</guid>
      <description>This course introduces public budgeting and finance. It emphasizes the budgetary process as both a political and management tool, essential for the operation and funding of public programs. Public managers will gain the knowledge and skills to understand key principles of budgeting and its role in expressing societal values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Administration in American Society</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/c1/</guid>
      <description>This course, taught at Florida State University from Fall 2021 to Spring 2022, introduced students to the fundamental theories and practices of public administration. Topics covered included social equity, public ethics, organizational theory, politics and management, public finance, performance management, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest Lectures</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/c2/</guid>
      <description>This page gathers information about the guest lectures I have provided for both master and doctoral level graduate students.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
