<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>environmental policy on Yixin Liu</title>
    <link>http://yixin-liu.com/tags/environmental-policy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in environmental policy on Yixin Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yixin-liu.com/tags/environmental-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A “watershed” moment for collaboration: The impacts of legislation and network governance on environmental outcomes</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/orwater/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/orwater/</guid>
      <description>This paper combines the regression discontinuity in time (RDiT) design and longitudinal analysis to examine the impacts of state legislation and the subsequent collaborative projects on water quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediating collaborations: The role of participant diversity in watershed governance</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/council/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/council/</guid>
      <description>This paper combines the difference-in-differences design and mediation analysis to examine the impacts of nonprofit watershed councils and the participant diversity on water quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reward exploitation or exploration? The effects of local government sustainability strategies and performance information on citizen evaluation</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/exploitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/exploitation/</guid>
      <description>This survey experiment finds that citizens evaluate government sustainability performance more favorably when it results from established policies (exploitation) rather than pioneering initiatives (exploration).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All hands on deck: The role of collaborative platforms and lead organizations in achieving environmental goals</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/ccc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/ccc/</guid>
      <description>This paper combines the difference-in-differences (DiD) methods and content analysis to examine the effectiveness of collaborative platforms in supporting local collaborations for natural resource management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effectiveness of network administrative organizations in governing inter-jurisdictional natural resources</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/rcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/rcs/</guid>
      <description>This paper uses the synthetic control method, incorporating monthly water quality data from 14 river monitoring sites in two neighboring cities, to examine the effectiveness of the Network Administrative Organization (NAO) model in reducing water pollution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
