<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>collaborative governance on Yixin Liu</title>
    <link>http://yixin-liu.com/tags/collaborative-governance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in collaborative governance on Yixin Liu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yixin-liu.com/tags/collaborative-governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All hands on deck: The role of collaborative platforms and lead organizations in achieving environmental goals</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/working/ccc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/working/ccc/</guid>
      <description>This paper combines the difference-in-differences (DiD) methods and content analysis to examine the effectiveness of collaborative platforms in supporting local collaborations for natural resource management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How and when democratic values matter: Challenging the effectiveness-centric framework in program evaluation</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/publication/liuleeberryppmr2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/publication/liuleeberryppmr2023/</guid>
      <description>Using a conjoint experiment, this research compare the effects of effectiveness and democratic values in predicting public program evaluation, conditioned on citizens’ trust in government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro foundations of interlocal collaboration: An experimental test</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/working/localexp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/working/localexp/</guid>
      <description>This paper uses a conjoint experiment involving U.S. municipal officials to compare three fundamental theories: rational choice, political homophily, and social capital, in predicting the willingness to collaborate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public trust and collaborative governance: an instrumental variable approach</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/publication/liupmr2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/publication/liupmr2022/</guid>
      <description>This research utilizes public integrity information, randomly assigned as the instrumental variable, to explore the impact of trust in government on citizens&amp;rsquo; perceptions of collaborative governance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effectiveness of network administrative organizations in governing inter-jurisdictional natural resources</title>
      <link>http://yixin-liu.com/publication/liutanpa2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yixin-liu.com/publication/liutanpa2022/</guid>
      <description>This paper uses the synthetic control method, incorporating monthly water quality data from 14 river monitoring sites in two neighboring cities, to examine the effectiveness of the Network Administrative Organization (NAO) model in reducing water pollution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
